Call to order the regular meeting of the Miami Special Utility Authority for today's date and time.
Item 2 is an invocation by Pastor of First Assembly of God.
Raymond, is he, Mr. Frizzell, here?
Chief, would you do the honors?
Father God, I thank you for this day, and I thank you for each person that attended here.
I thank you, Father, for the leadership that Dean provides and the direction that the council provides.
I pray, God, that you would watch over them, watch over their families.
I ask that you be with the city employees and protect us.
I ask that this meeting be guided in a way that's pleasing to you.
It's in Jesus' name I pray. Amen.
Brian, would you do the point, please?
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America
and to the republic for which it stands,
one nation under God, indivisible, with liberty and justice,
for all.
Thank you, Brian.
Thank you, Chief.
Item 4 is public input and unscheduled personal appearances.
Anyone of the audience that wishes to address the authority on any agenda items?
There being none, Item 5 is consent agenda.
Staff is recommending Items 6 through 11 for the consent agenda.
If there are no questions on any of those items, I'd entertain a motion.
I must do it for the mayor.
And a second?
Second.
Roll call, please.
Johnson?
Aye.
Weston?
Winchester?
Aye.
Lewis?
Schultz?
Aye.
Item 12 is new business.
Any new business?
Anyone?
Item 13, staff reports in your packet, if available.
And the staff's present if there are any questions.
Item 14 is trustee community announcements.
Anyone have any announcements?
I had asked the utility department's billing staff recently to give me some examples of some
of their cut-off process that they go through.
We've had a couple of complaints about the amount of the fee that's charged for the cut-off
and then to re-establish service.
And so I asked them to give me some examples of that, which I have and have kind of looked
at.
I'm just letting you know at a future utility authority meeting, I may want to revisit that.
We passed an ordinance a couple of years ago, and it's been in effect now for a couple of
years.
And I think some of it bears going back and looking at.
So just to kind of...
Actually, I think that's been in effect for last year.
So it's probably just fun that we take a look and see how it's affecting it.
So just a heads up, and I'll ask them to share the information that I have and kind of the
general nature prior to that time.
Item 15 is adjournment.
Do we have a motion to adjourn the SUA meeting?
I'll make a motion.
And a second, please.
I'll second it.
Roll call.
Forrester?
Aye.